[
    {
      "numb": 1,
      "question": "I came _____ America",
      "answer": "from",
      "options": [
        "from",
        "at",
        "in",
        "on"
      ]
    },
    {
      "numb": 2,
      "question": "I ____ cold.",
      "answer": "am",
      "options": [
        "am",
        "have",
        "had",
        "is"
      ]
    },
    {
      "numb": 3,
      "question": "________ car is very old fashioned.",
      "answer": "Fatima's",
      "options": [
        "Fatima's",
        "Fatimas",
        "Fatima is",
        "Fatimas'"
      ]
    },
    {
      "numb": 4,
      "question": "I speak English but he_______.",
      "answer": "doesn't speaks",
      "options": [
        "doesn't speaks",
        "doesn't speak",
        "speaks",
        "don't speak"
      ]
    },
    {
      "numb": 5,
      "question": "Nowadays everyone ______ internet.",
      "answer": "uses",
      "options": [
        "had used",
        "uses",
        "used",
        "use"
      ]
    },
    {
      "numb": 6,
      "question": "______ there anybody in the room?",
      "answer": "is",
      "options": [
        "Are",
        "is",
        "am",
        "if"
      ]
    },
    {
      "numb": 7,
      "question": "What___ you doing?",
      "answer": "are",
      "options": [
        "is",
        "are",
        "am",
        "if"
      ]
    },
    {
      "numb": 8,
      "question": "Which book is ______?",
      "answer": "yours",
      "options": [
        "your",
        "your's",
        "yours",
        "your is"
      ]
    },
    {
      "numb": 9,
      "question": "She is____ home.",
      "answer": "at",
      "options": [
        "at",
        "in",
        "on",
        "from"
      ]
    },
    {
      "numb": 10,
      "question": "Why _____ she come late?",
      "answer": "dose",
      "options": [
        "do",
        "dose",
        "is",
        "are"
      ]
    }
  ]